Welcome to exercise number 53, we are asked to write a function to reverse the link of least.
It's very important and common question that you may see in the university or interview.
We will make it as if they are actively and and recursive.
OK, so OK, let's start.
We will create public
void for iterative return, not reverse.
Last.
And it took.
No, no.
OK.
Both the video and think about how we could make a method that would reverse the link at lest
we start by not brave equal to none.
No current equal to know that we have passed.
So we are referring the current known as the not that it's best and not next equal to nothing.
Now let's see.
We need to pass through all that that list and reach the end and start from the end to tell him.
So while Grant does not equal to null,
then next equal to Karen thought next year on moving and cursor by next equals current the next current
dot next equal to previous.
Moving the carrier now prev equal to current and current.
Equal to next.
OK, it's very simple.
Now we have and that from making that while loop this word, refer to the next year with regard to next
and move the current to the previous and the previous.
Equal to guarantee guarantee equal to next.
I'm just making this happen to return previous and return now.
They're not actually making the previous return in the previous act.
OK, now let's see how to reverse this link.
At least this is that while loop that we have created, we have created three objects of nonce and the
pointers to them.
Previous, current and next.
And we have moved this cursor to become at the end and the start from the end to return there.
Not note.
OK.
No.
In order to use this, I will make less the reverse.
We will reverse this list and pass the hand, and then we will print it again.
Let's see, we go to the main.
If we will exercise number
fifty three, we will reverse reverse the last
link, at least Doug reversed list and we passed that link and placed the tab and then linked list that
print a list.
OK, let me see.
And here we go.
We didn't pass anything from here.
I think we have removed this, removing the duplicates that we see four one five three five.
I check it again.
OK, I think the problem is in the print list, so we go to the print list.
I will change it to become more professional.
It does not, as the first wave not, does not.
I will remove this while not node does not equal to no node here and node.
This will be more, more specific so we can print from the head.
And from that they.
We need to pass that at to TED here in order to print it.
And here I think at least from the head and now linked list also with the head.
OK, so linked list not had this.
Is that reversed?
System that allowed the brand to reverse this.
Let's.
OK.
We have four one five three five we have removed the duplicates, four one, five three and the reversed
list.
We didn't make anything from the listing, at least at that.
We are going to print the list of the reverse.
OK, I will change this card.
And based.
That reverse link, at least with the head, let me see.
And here we go, guys, we have reversed it.
This is the linked list that we have for one 540.
We have reversed it correctly.
Three five one four.
OK, so this is the way that we make our reversing for that link at list.
OK.
And iterative, we will see in the next video how to make it at like a recursively.
And it's very important to understand how it works.
Recursive.
OK.